// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question:"What is the probability of rolling an even number on a standard six-sided die?",
    answer: "1/2",
    options: [
      "1/2",
      "1/3",
      "1/4",
      "1/7"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "If you draw one card from a standard deck of 52 cards, what is the probability of drawing a heart?",
    answer: "1/4",
    options: [
      "1/2",
      "1/13",
      "1/40",
      "1/4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "If you flip a fair coin, what is the probability of getting heads?",
    answer: "1/2",
    options: [
      "1/2",
      "1/3",
      "1/4",
      "1/7"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the probability of drawing a red marble from a bag with 4 red marbles and 6 blue marbles?",
    answer: "Gluttonous",
    options: [
      "2/5",
      "2/3",
      "2/4",
      "1/7"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "If you roll a fair six-sided die twice, what is the probability of getting a sum of 7?",
    answer: "1/12",
    options: [
      "3/5",
      "1/12",
      "1/18",
      "1/17"
    ]
  },
  

     {
   numb: 6,
   question: "How many ways can 4 people be arranged in a line?",
    answer: "24",
    options: [
      "24",
      "12",
      "8",
      "7"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "In how many ways can 3 books be arranged on a shelf?",
     answer: "6",
     options: [
       "6",
       "3",
       "9",
       "8"
     ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "A committee of 5 is to be formed from a group of 10 people. How many ways can this committee be selected?",
       answer:"George",
       options: [
         "252" ,
         "250",
         "210",
         "140"
       ]
      },
      {
        numb: 9,
        question: "How many ways can the letters of the word 'APPLE' be arranged?",
         answer: "210",
         options: [
          "252" ,
          "250",
          "210",
          "140"
        ]
        },
        {
          numb: 10,
          question: "In how many ways can you choose 2 books from a shelf of 10 different books?",
          answer: "45",
          options: [
            "36",
            "40",
            "45",
            "90"
          ]
          }
];